findemployment.com 2016-07-02

# Privacy Policy | FindEmployment

This Privacy Statement incorporates by reference the Terms of Use for the FE Network which apply to this Privacy Statement. Please review this Privacy Statement periodically as we may update it from time to time.

WHY DO WE NEED YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

When you use the Services provided on the FE Network, you may be asked to provide certain personal information such as your name, age, education, contact details, etc. This information will be stored safely and confidentially. We will use this information in the following ways:

\- To register you with the FE Network and administer the FE Network’s Services where you have registered to receive them. You can unsubscribe from these Services at any time;

\- To administer any contest or other promotional offer you may enter and to notify winners;

\- To answer any queries which you may send to us through the FE Network internal mail, external e-mail, or customer support system;

\- In order to conduct customer satisfaction and employment-related surveys;

\- To meet our legal compliance obligations;

\- For crime prevention and detection; and,

\- For direct marketing purposes, as set out in detail below.

HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

Information you provide or that is obtained by us will be used by us to enable us to review, develop, and improve the Services which we offer and provide you and other Users (via internal mail, external e-mail, or otherwise) with information about new products and Services and special offers we think you will find valuable. We may also inform you about new products and services and special offers of selected third parties.

TO WHOM WE DISCLOSE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

We do not sell or trade your personal information to third parties, if you have indicated a desire for us to keep the information private. When you use our Services, you decide for yourself how much contact or other personal information you wish to display.

We may give information about you as follows:

\- We may provide our third party service providers and processors with access to your personal information. These service providers may include: credit or debit card verification providers and payment processors; our customer support centre; marketing organizations who may market and promote our Services; internet service providers who administer the FE Network, provide internet services, and host our facilities; and/or consumer research companies that assist us with understanding consumer interests by conducting surveys. We only share your personal information to the extent required for the performance of Services. We implemented safeguards to ensure that our service providers treat personal information in a way that is consistent with the terms of this Privacy Statement and that it is never used except to fulfill our Services to our users. We may also disclose your personal information as permitted or required by law. For example, we will disclose personal information to those governmental bodies, who have authority to obtain it, in order to comply with a warrant or subpoena issued by a court of a competent jurisdiction, and to comply with record production requirements.

\- In the event of sale of all or substantially all of the assets of DeltaQuest Media, we may transfer personal information in our control to a third party purchaser that agrees to use personal information for the same reasons identified in this Privacy Statement.

\- To anyone to whom we transfer or may transfer our rights and duties under our Agreement with you.

\- If we have a duty to do so or if the law allows us to do so.

\- To our employees and agents to do any of the above on our behalf, now or in the future.

If you choose not to provide certain personal information we request, you will still be able to visit the FE Network but you may be unable to access certain options or Services offered by the FE Network.

YOUR CONSENT

By choosing to provide us with your personal information, you are consenting to its use in accordance with the principles outlined in this Privacy Statement and as outlined at the time you are asked to provide any personal information. DeltaQuest Media may contact you by e-mail or otherwise in order to provide you with updates pertaining to the Services, as well as information about additional offers, products, or events that DeltaQuest Media believes may be of interest to you. You can choose to unsubscribe from these updates or from having your personal information used for market research purposes.

WITHDRAWING YOUR CONSENT

DeltaQuest Media provides you with a way to withdraw your consent for any of the marketing communications received by you via external e-mail or otherwise. If you no longer wish to receive promotional materials you may opt out of receiving these communications by visiting the relevant page on the FE Network or sending a relevant request to our customer support centre. This will remove you from the FE Network promotions lists. Please note that if you do not consent to the use and disclosure of your personal information, this may affect our ability to provide you with particular products and Services.

SECURITY

We will take appropriate steps to protect the personal information you share with us. We have implemented technology and security features to safeguard the privacy of your personal information.

COOKIES

There is a technology called "cookies" which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a web site. A cookie is an element of data that a web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. Some FE Network pages may use cookies so that we can better serve you when you return to our sites. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it or not. For more information, please see information readily available on the Internet of "How to Work with Cookies".

AGGREGATE DATA

We may aggregate personal information and remove any identifying elements in order to analyze patterns and improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze use of FE the Network, to improve our content and product offerings, and to customize our content, layout, and Services.

We gather certain usage information like the number and frequency of visitors to the FE Network. This information may include which URL you came from, which URL you next go to, what browser you are using, and your IP address. We only use such data in the aggregate. This collective data helps us to determine how much our customers use certain parts and services of the FE Network, and do internal research on our users’ demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand and serve you.

ACCESS TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

You have the right to see personal information we keep about you. We will endeavor to provide the information you require within a reasonable time. If you are concerned that any of the information we hold on you is incorrect, please log in to your Account with the FE Network and update your information.

TRANSFER OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Some parties that process or store personal information may be located in jurisdictions outside your country of residence. Therefore, your information may be processed and stored in these jurisdictions and, as a result, foreign governments, courts, or law enforcement or regulatory agencies may be able to obtain disclosure of your information through the laws in these countries.

NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES

If we decide to change our Privacy Statement, we will post those changes on the FE Network, so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under which circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify you by way of external e-mail or otherwise. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the Privacy Statement under which the information was collected. You agree that by using the FE Network, you are expressly and affirmatively consenting to our use and disclosure of the information that you provide, and consenting to receive e-mails and other communications as described above.

COMPLAINTS RESOLUTION

DeltaQuest Media cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Statement. Therefore, although we are committed to protecting your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private. As a user of the FE Network, you understand and agree that you assume all responsibility and risk for your use of the FE Network, the internet generally, and the documents you post or access, and for your conduct on and off the FE Network.

We are committed to providing a fair and responsive system for handling and resolving complaints concerning the handling of personal information. You have a right to complain and to have your complaint handled efficiently if you are concerned about our handling of your personal information. We believe that any complaint that we may receive is a valuable opportunity to improve the Services that we deliver to you and to maintain your confidence in our Services. If at any time you wish to lodge a complaint in respect of the handling, use, or disclosure of your personal information by us, you may do so by contacting our Customer Support Centre by following the ‘Contact Us’ link provided at the footer or header on each page of the FE Network.
